(Sheldon:)Anyway, you're aware that Leonard has
entered into a new romantic relationship...
(Sheldon:)...which includes a sexual component.
- Okay, feeling the awkward now.
- Wait.
(Sheldon:)Her name is Dr. Stephanie Barnett.
And she's a highly distinguished
surgical resident at Fremont Memorial.
- Yeah, Leonard told me.
- Good.
(Sheldon:)What he may have left out
is how important this relationship is to me.
- To you?
- Yes.
(Sheldon:)See, of the handful of women
Leonard's been involved with...
(Sheldon:)...she's the only one
I have ever found tolerable.
(Penny:)Well, what about me?
(Sheldon:)The statement stands for itself.
(Penny:)Well, aren't you sweet?
(Sheldon:)Anyway, should you have
any interaction with her...
(Sheldon:)...it would be most helpful
that she not see you as a sexual rival.
PENNY:
Yeah, I think she's pretty safe.
(Sheldon:)You say that now,
but consider the following scenario.